<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on cheger.land</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on cheger.land</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Various Tools</title>
      <link>/post/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 20:23:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tools/</guid>
      <description>sent  tool for presentations based on Takahashi method minimal, easy to write  mathpix  screenshot of any equation to LaTeX unfortunately only for Mac and mobiles There is a small workaround for Linux. Mathpix is based on an API that you can call up to 1000 times per month for free. So just get an API key, create a file eqtotex.py  #!/usr/bin/env python # imports import sys import base64 import requests import json # file path of picture file_path = str(sys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D3 Animations in Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/anim/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 18:02:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/anim/</guid>
      <description> I can also put my animation easily into these posts.  Like this small animation about quantum friction:      Try and drag the top atom around! Depending on whether you switched the material response on or off the mirroratom will or will not follow the motion of the atom above the material. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Library Management Done Right</title>
      <link>/post/library/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 15:09:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/library/</guid>
      <description>It is really useful to keep a central place where you put all interesting things you find on the internet like Books, Websites, Articles, &amp;hellip; . For me this central place is Zotero.
How my library is organized I like keeping four sublibraries for  textbooks my own calculations, transcripts and reviews papers, articles, theses and similar
 websites  in which I don&amp;rsquo;t have any further ordering.
Adding a new entry The feature I like most about Zotero is the Zotero Connector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To: This Website</title>
      <link>/post/website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 16:12:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/website/</guid>
      <description>I have been searching long and wide for an easy to make and easy to maintain website. Most things sucked until I found out about R Markdown Websites. You basically write your content in markdown and then R Markdown handles everything for you. It was certainly a way to do it and for everyone who wants to try I can recommend:
 Nick Strayer
 Robert Mitchell
  There were however some issues that bothered me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>